<?xml version="1.0"?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">SAP to Salesforce contact migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
		Use this template if would like to sync Contacts from SAP to Salesforce in manner of one time synchronization by hitting the HTTP endpoint. 
		Inbound SAP endpoint retrieves all Contacts in SAP using standard BAPI  **BAPI_CUSTOMER_GETCONTACTLIST** and transforms them to Salesforce Contacts
		In this template you may choose whether Account for Contact should be created as well during the migration process. 
		This functionality relies on standard BAPI for retrieving details about customers **BAPI_CUSTOMER_GETDETAIL2**
		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
		<![CDATA[
To make this Anypoint Template run, there are certain preconditions that must be considered.
All of them deal with the preparations in both source (SAP) and destination (SFDC) systems, that must be made in order for everything to run smoothly.
**Failling to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**

Before using this Anypoint Template, you may want to check out this [Documentation Page](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/SAP+Connector#SAPConnector-EnablingYourStudioProjectforSAP), that will teach you how to work 
with SAP and Anypoint Studio-

## Disclaimer

This Anypoint template uses a few private Maven dependencies in oder to work. If you intend to run this template with Maven support, please continue reading.

You will find that there are three dependencies in the pom.xml file that begin with the following group id: 
	**com.sap.conn.jco** 
These dependencies are private for Mulesoft and will cause you application not to build from a Maven command line. You need to replace them with "provided" scope and copy the libraries into the build path.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="sap_src">
<![CDATA[
4. Partner profile
Partner profile needs to be customized type of logical system as partner type. Outbound parameter of message type MATMAS is defined in the partner profile. As receiver port an RFC destination created earlier is used. Idoc Type MATMAS01 is defined.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="sfdc_dst">
		<![CDATA[

		</section>
		<section id="running_on_studio">
		<![CDATA[
In order to make this Anypoint Template run on Anypoint Studio there are a few extra steps that needs to be made.
Please check this Documentation Page:

+ [Enabling Your Studio Project for SAP](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/SAP+Connector#SAPConnector-EnablingYourStudioProjectforSAP)
		]]>
		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
		<![CDATA[
**SAP Connector configuration**

+ sap.jco.ashost `your.sap.address.com`
+ sap.jco.user `SAP_USER`
+ sap.jco.passwd `SAP_PASS`
+ sap.jco.sysnr `14`
+ sap.jco.client `800`
+ sap.jco.lang `EN`

**SalesForce Connector configuration**

+ sfdc.username `bob.dylan@sfdc`
+ sfdc.password `DylanPassword123`
+ sfdc.securityToken `avsfwCUl7apQs56Xq2AKi3X`
+ sfdc.url `https://test.salesforce.com/services/Soap/u/32.0`

**SMTP Services configuration**

+ smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
+ smtp.port `587`
+ smtp.user `gmailuser`
+ smtp.password `gmailpassword`

**Mail details**

+ mail.from `your.email@gmail.com`
+ mail.to `your.email@gmail.com`
+ mail.subject `Mail subject`

**Policy for creating accounts in SF syncAccount, doNotCreateAccount**

+ account.sync.policy `syncAccount`
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">
		<![CDATA[
SalesForce imposes limits on the number of API Calls that can be made.
Therefore calculating this amount may be an important factor to
consider. Product Broadcast Template calls to the API can be
calculated using the formula:

**X * 3 + X / 200**

Being X the number of Contacts to be synchronized on each run.

Multiplication by 3 is because for every user if account.sync.policy is set to value **syncAccounts** for every contact will be checked
if an account with matching name exists in Salesforce and if not it will be created.

The division by 200 is because, by default, contacts are gathered in groups
of 200 for each Upsert API Call in the commit step. 

For instance if 10 records are fetched from origin instance, then 31 api
calls to SFDC will be made (worst case scenario). If accounts already exist or syncing of accounts is disabled, there will be fewer API calls made.
]]>
		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>